Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-890. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 890, General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1952 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      March 17, 1952-June 24, 1952. "Case of Mart Moore"
    - Lodge No. 890, General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1949-1951 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      December 28, 1949-June 19, 1951. "Appeal H.C. Carrasco"
    - Lodge No. 890, General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1952-1956 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      February 18, 1952-May 17, 1956.
    - Lodge No. 890, General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1947-1952 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      June 5, 1947-January 1, 1952.
    - Lodge No. 890, General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1921-1947 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      October 31, 1921-May 8, 1947.
  - Sub-Series 235-891. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 891, Mason City Lodge, Mason City, Iowa, 1922-1959 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      January 21, 1922-April 7, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1480, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, effective January 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-892. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 892, Charleston Lodge, Charleston, South Carolina, 1937-1960 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      July 26, 1937-October 18, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1046, Charleston, South Carolina, effective July 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 892, Stonewall Lodge, Trinidad, Colorado, 1922-1923 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      February 8, 1922-April 11, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-894. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 894, Britt, Ontario, Canada, 1937-1958 (Box 136, Folder 16)
      August 10, 1937-March 24, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 940, Little Current, Ontario, Canada, effective January 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-895. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 895, Crookston Lodge, Crookston, Minnesota, 1930-1961 (Box 136, Folder 17)
      April 14, 1930-February 1, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 488, Grand Forks, North Dakota, effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-897. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 897, Jere Baxter Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1942-1969 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      August 27, 1942-June 27, 1969. Disbanded, effective July 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-899. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 899, Vineyard Lines Lodge, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1937-1946 (Box 136, Folder 19)
      August 7, 1937-May 29, 1946. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-903. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 903, Carlin Lodge, Carlin, Nevada, 1937-1939 (Box 136, Folder 20)
      August 6, 1937-August 31, 1939. Consolidated with Lodge No. 911, Sacramento, California, effective August 21, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-906. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 906, Wabash Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1960 (Box 136, Folder 21)
      September 29, 1921-November 29, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-910. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 910, R. S. Beatty Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1921-1959 (Box 136, Folder 22)
      September 30, 1921-November 6, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-911. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 911, Central District Lodge, Roseville, California, 1937-1963 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      August 12, 1937-November 22, 1963. Moved from Sacramento, California
  - Sub-Series 235-913. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 913, John W. Walker Lodge, Victoria, Texas, 1929-1959 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      July 31, 1929-April 3, 1959. Formerly Southern Pacific Lodge
    - Lodge No. 913, Ennis Lodge, Ennis, Texas, 1924 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      September 15, 1924-October 1, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 235-914. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 914, Oneida Lodge, Oneida, New York, 1927-1957 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      February 26, 1927-October 3, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1067, Rome, New York, effective July 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-915. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 915, Beardstown Lodge, Beardstown, Illinois, 1926-1962 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      November 17, 1926-February 5, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 159, Centralia, Illinois, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-916. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 916, Collar City Lodge, Troy, New York, 1949-1968 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      April, 1949-October 19, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 861, Albany, New York, effective October 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-917. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 917, Atlantic Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1938-1942 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      June 8, 1938-May 29, 1942. Disbanded, effective May 29, 1942
    - Lodge No. 917, Shawnee Lodge, New York, New York, 1937 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      August 12-13, 1937.
    - Lodge No. 917, Capitol City Lodge, Olympia, Washington, 1923-1926 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      October 18, 1923-February 20, 1926.
  - Sub-Series 235-918. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 918, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1942-1943 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      August 24, 1942-July 28, 1943. Suspended, effective July 28, 1943
    - Lodge No. 918, Clyde Mallory Lodge, New York, New York, 1939-1942 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      January 19, 1939-January 21, 1942. Formerly Shawnee Lodge; disbanded, effective January 21, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-918. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 918, Globe Lodge, Globe, Arizona, 1922 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      February 20, 1922-March 30, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-920. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 920, Cotton Belt General Office Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      July 5-7, 1922. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1299, Tyler, Texas, effective July 1, 1954 -August 17, 1937-April 30, 1956 / Lodge No. 920, Quinnipiac Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut
  - Sub-Series 235-922. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 922, Bison City Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1921-1956 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      December 29, 1921-November 12, 1956.
    - Lodge No. 922, Bison City Lodge, Buffalo, New York, Subject: "Special File on Controversy in Lodge No. 922 resulting in removal of Brother George J. Hertel, President", 1953-1954 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      December 2, 1953-December 27, 1954.
  - Sub-Series 235-924. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 924, Coral Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1937-1938 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      August 26, 1937-September 28, 1938. Suspended, effective September 28, 1938
    - Lodge No. 924, Riverside Lodge, Riverside, California, 1930 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      May 4, 1930-August 15, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-925. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 925, Rock Island Lodge, Muscatine, Iowa, 1931-1960 (Box 137, Folder 12)
      December 24, 1931-April 18, 1960. Formerly Pearl City Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 417, Rock Island, Illinois, effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-926. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 926, Golden Spike Lodge, Ogden, Utah, 1924-1962 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      April 4, 1924-December 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-927. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 927, Capitol City Lodge, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1937-1959 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      August 26, 1937-July 16, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1125, Wichita, Kansas, effective July 1, 1959
    - Lodge No. 927, Steamship Checkers' Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1922-1923 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      June 22, 1922-June 10, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-931. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 931, Champlain Lodge, Plattsburgh, New York, 1939-1961 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      October 17, 1939-November 1, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 764, Rouses Point, New York, Lodge No. 872, Saratoga Springs, New York, and Lodge No. 874, Whitehall, New York, effective October 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 931, Susquehanna Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1937-1938 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      9/3/1937-7/7/1938.
  - Sub-Series 235-934. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 934, Ludington Lodge, Ludington, Michigan, 1928-1951 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      October 24, 1928-February 20, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 810, Ludington, Michigan, effective January 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-935. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 935, Niles Lodge, Niles, Michigan, 1921-1962 (Box 137, Folder 17)
      1921-April 24, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 338, Kalamazoo, Michigan, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-936. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 936, Galveston General Office Lodge, Galveston, Texas, 1937-1966 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      September 17, 1937-February 2, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 193, Temple, Texas, Lodge No. 427, Topeka, Kansas, and Lodge No. 1079, Amarillo, Texas, effective January 1, 1966
    - Lodge No. 936, Hocking Valley Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1924 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      November 8, 1924-December 1, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 235-937. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 937, Rock Island Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1958 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      September 14, 1922-May 15, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 767, Kansas City, Missouri, effective May 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-938. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 938, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1942-1943 (Box 137, Folder 20)
      August 25, 1942-July 28, 1943. Disbanded, effective July 28, 1943
    - Lodge No. 938, Tri-Terminal Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1937-1941 (Box 137, Folder 20)
      September 17, 1937-November 11, 1941. Consolidated with Lodge No. 773, Brooklyn, New York, effective November 11, 1941
  - Sub-Series 235-939. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 939, Richelieu Lodge, Quebec, Quebec, Canada, 1939-1950 (Box 137, Folder 21)
      October 24, 1939-November 20, 1950.
    - Lodge No. 939, Lehigh Valley General Office Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1937-1938 (Box 137, Folder 21)
      September 17, 1937-February 4, 1938. Consolidated with Lodge No. 930, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, effective February 3, 1938
    - Lodge No. 939, Orange Lodge, Port Jervis, New York, 1922 (Box 137, Folder 21)
      July 27, 1922-August 8, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-940. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 940, Hudson Lodge, Cliffside Park, New Jersey, 1937-1938 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      September 7, 1937-April 9, 1938. Surrendered charter, effective April 5, 1938
    - Lodge No. 940, Deerfield Lodge, Greenfield, Massachusetts, 1931-1933 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      May 18, 1931-November 22, 1933.
    - Lodge No. 940, Penn Lodge, Williamsport, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      August 13, 1921-October 3, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-943. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1956-1962 (Box 137, Folder 23)
      November 28, 1956-December 17, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1947-1956 (Box 137, Folder 24)
      January 10, 1947-October 29, 1956.
    - 235-943(a). Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia(a). Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1935-1946 (Box 137, Folder 25)
      February 16, 1935-December 6, 1946.
    - 235-943(b). Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1930-1943 (Box 137, Folder 26)
      May 26, 1930-June 18, 1943.
    - 235-943(b). Lodge No. 943, Washington Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1923-1928 (Box 137, Folder 26)
      March 2, 1923-September 12, 1928.
  - Sub-Series 235-945. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 945, Jean Lafitte Lodge, Galveston, Texas, 1937-1961 (Box 137, Folder 27)
      October 6, 1937-February 10, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 873, Galveston, Texas, effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-946. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 946, Ft. William, Ontario, Canada, 1943-1945 (Box 137, Folder 28)
      January 27, 1943-March 10, 1945. Disbanded?
    - Lodge No. 946, Coronation Lodge, Argentia, Newfoundland, Canada, 1937-1942 (Box 137, Folder 29)
      October 6, 1937-September 23, 1942. Disbanded, effective September 23, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-948. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 948, Vincennes, Indiana, 1931-1933 (Box 137, Folder 30)
      October 9, 1931-August 10, 1933. Suspended, effective September 30, 1932
  - Sub-Series 235-953. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 953, Swift Current Lodge, Swift Current, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1921-1966 (Box 137, Folder 31)
      November 17, 1921-September 29, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 665, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-955. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 955, General Putnam Lodge, Putnam, Connecticut, 1941-1961 (Box 137, Folder 32)
      July 8, 1941-February 17, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 186, Hartford, Connecticut, and Lodge No. 2166, Hartford, Connecticut, effective January 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 955, Frankfort Lodge, Frankfort, Indiana, 1921-1923 (Box 137, Folder 32)
      December 14, 1921-March 3, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-956. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 956, McAdoo Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1921-1966 (Box 137, Folder 33)
      January 14, 1921-September 6, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1020, Atlanta, Georgia, effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-958. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 958, Brookhattan Lodge, New York, New York, 1937-1965 (Box 137, Folder 34)
      October 14, 1937-November 19, 1965. Consolidated with Lodge No. 657, Empire State Lodge, New York, New York, effective October 1, 1965
    - Lodge No. 958, Breckenridge Lodge, Breckenridge, Minnesota, 1922 (Box 137, Folder 34)
      February 24, 1922-March 2, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-959. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 959, Hillsboro Lodge, Hillsboro, Illinois, 1922-1959 (Box 137, Folder 35)
      January 27, 1922-August 17, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 795, Mattoon, Illinois, effective July 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-960. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 960, Hill Billy Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1932-1965 (Box 137, Folder 36)
      October 18, 1932-November 30, 1965. Formerly Orange Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 967, Paterson, New Jersey, effective October 1, 1965
    - Lodge No. 960, Classic City Lodge, Stratford, Ontario, Canada, 1923 (Box 137, Folder 36)
      February 21, 1923-March 30, 1923.
  - Sub-Series 235-961. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 961, Harlan County Lodge, Loyall, Kentucky, 1942-1960 (Box 137, Folder 37)
      September 3, 1942-May 13, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1367, Middlesboro, Kentucky, effective April 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 961, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1937-1939 (Box 137, Folder 37)
      October 28, 1937-January 23, 1939.
  - Sub-Series 235-964. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 964, Rock Island General Office Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1949 (Box 137, Folder 38)
      November 22, 1929-October 10, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 235-965. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 965, Franklin D Lodge, Secaucus, New Jersey, 1937-1965 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      November 3, 1937-December 2, 1965. Consolidated with Lodge No. 331, Hoboken, New Jersey, effective October 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-966. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 966, Pana, Illinois, 1923-1959 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      July 7, 1923-August 24, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 167, Springfield, Illinois, and Lodge No. 795, Mattoon, Illinois, effective July 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-968. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 968, Port Morris Lodge, Port Morris, New Jersey, 1937-1962 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      November 3, 1937-February 27, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 960, Newark, New Jersey, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-971. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 971, Fort Schuyler Lodge, Utica, New York, 1937-1962 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      November 3, 1937-February 27, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 206, Binghamton, New York, Lodge No. 974, Syracuse, New York, and Lodge No. 1610, Syracuse, New York, effective January 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 971, Peoria, Illinois, 1923 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      1923 July 7
  - Sub-Series 235-975. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 975, Boston Terminal Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1924-1942 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      May 20, 1924-October 30, 1942. Consolidated with Lodge No. 143, Boston, Massachusetts, effective July 27, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-976. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 976, Sherman Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1937-1943 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      November 11, 1937-May 7, 1943. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-978. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 978, Starved Rock Lodge, LaSalle, Illinois, 1921-1966 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      August 19, 1921-January 18, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 272, Joliet, Illinois, Lodge No. 633, Aurora, Illinois, Lodge No. 767, Kansas City, Missouri, and Lodge No. 2033, Galesburg, Illinois, effective January 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-979. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 979, Rock River Lodge, Rockford, Illinois, 1923-1968 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      November 28, 1923-November 25, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 231, Green Bay, Wisconsin, Lodge No. 633, Aurora, Illinois, Lodge No. 881, Freeport, Illinois, and Lodge No. 1312, Sterling, Illinois, effective October 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-980. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 980, Kingston, Pennsylvania, 1937-1966 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      November 11, 1937-May 9, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 949, Scranton, Pennsylvania, effective April 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-981. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 981, Seattle, Washington, 1937-1953 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      November 17, 1937-September 30, 1953. Disbanded, effective September 30, 1953
    - Lodge No. 981, Chickasha Subdivision Lodge, Lawton, Oklahoma, 1925 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      September 7-29, 1925.
  - Sub-Series 235-982. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 982, Norwich Lodge, Norwich, New York, 1931-1958 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      April 6, 1931-January 23, 1958. Consolidated with Lodge No. 788, Oneonta, New York, effective December 31, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-983. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 983, Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1939-1953 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      December 28, 1939-October 16, 1953. Formerly Fortieth Anniversary Lodge
    - Lodge No. 983, Unity Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1937-1939 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      November 26, 1937-July 17, 1939. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1, Cincinnati, Ohio, effective July 17, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-986. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 986, Hudson Harbor Lodge, New York, New York, 1938-1959 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      January 20, 1938-April 23, 1959.
    - Lodge No. 986, Greenville, Mississippi, 1930 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      December 8-16, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-988. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 988, Lyons Lodge, Lyons, New York, 1933-1965 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      April 15, 1933-March 30, 1965. Consolidated with Lodge No. 252, Syracuse, New York, Lodge No. 1215, Rochester, New York, and Lodge No. 1373, East Rochester, New York, effective January 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-989. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 989, Fort Pierce, Florida, 1927 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      1927 October 12. Disbanded, effective October 12, 1927
  - Sub-Series 235-991. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 991, Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific General Office Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1957 (Box 138, Folder 17)
      January 13, 1922-June 11, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-992. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 992, Progress Lodge, Woburn, Massachusetts, 1928-1961 (Box 138, Folder 18)
      September 5, 1928-September 11, 1961.
    - Lodge No. 992, Mile High Lodge, Prescott, Arizona, 1921-1922 (Box 138, Folder 18)
      October 5, 1921-February 18, 1922. Consolidated with Lodge No. 813, Winslow, Arizona, effective February 18, 1922
  - Sub-Series 235-997. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 997, DuQuoin Lodge, DuQuoin, Illinois, 1921-1922 (Box 138, Folder 19)
      December 21, 1921-January 14, 1922?. Disbanded, effective January 14, 1922?
  - Sub-Series 235-998. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 998, Baraboo Lodge, Baraboo, Wisconsin, 1926-1954 (Box 138, Folder 20)
      June 11, 1926-February 26, 1954. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1163, Chicago, Illinois, effective January 1, 1954
  - Sub-Series 235-999. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 999, Hobson Lodge, Hobson, Ohio, 1942-1961 (Box 138, Folder 21)
      June 23, 1942-January 16, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 429, Charleston, West Virginia, effective January 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 999, Picton, Ontario, Canada, 1938-1941 (Box 138, Folder 21)
      February 9, 1938-August 19, 1941. Suspended, effective August 19, 1941
    - Lodge No. 999, Clover Leaf Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1922 (Box 138, Folder 21)
      January 1, 1922-November 12, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1001. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1001, Lake City Lodge, Dunkirk, New York, 1934-1962 (Box 138, Folder 22)
      January 23, 1934-January 26, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 371, Erie, Pennsylvania, and Lodge No. 678, Salamanca, New York, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1003. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1003, Miller-Dale Lodge, Cumberland, Maryland, 1945-1961 (Box 138, Folder 23)
      December 18, 1945-December 21, 1961.
    - Lodge No. 1003, American Lodge, Hornell, New York, 1941-1943 (Box 138, Folder 24)
      July 24, 1941-August 10, 1943. Disbanded, effective July 23, 1943
  - Sub-Series 235-1005. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1005, Ithaca Lodge, Ithaca, New York, 1923-1962 (Box 138, Folder 25)
      September 21, 1923-February 9, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 578, Sayre, Pennsylvania, and Lodge No. 2217, Binghamton, New York, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1006. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1006, Michigan Central Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1933-1956 (Box 138, Folder 26)
      September 8, 1933-September 13, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 935, Niles, Michigan, and Lodge No. 1269, Chicago, Illinois, effective July 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-1008. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1008, Rainbow Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1922-1961 (Box 138, Folder 27)
      November 27, 1922-January 31, 1961. Suspended September 14, 1949, reinstated December 5, 1949, consolidated with Lodge 502, Newark, Ohio effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1011. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1011, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1941-1960 (Box 138, Folder 28)
      August 11, 1941-August 5, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 641, Ogden, Utah effective July 1, 1960 / Lodge No. 1011, Ogden, Utah
  - Sub-Series 235-1012. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1012, CB & Q Lodge, Wymore, Nebraska, 1950-1960 (Box 138, Folder 29)
      May 3, 1950-March 28, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 157, Lincoln, Nebraska effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1013. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1013, Hamline Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1925-1969 (Box 138, Folder 30)
      November 10, 1925-April 9, 1969.
  - Sub-Series 235-1015. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1015, Bay Line Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1932-1951 (Box 138, Folder 31)
      June 28, 1932-February 21, 1951. Disbanded effective February 20, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1018. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1018, Chicago Great Western Railway Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1960-1968 (Box 138, Folder 32)
      January 6, 1960-October 24, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 129, Winona, Minnesota, Lodge No. 369, Boone, Iowa, Lodge No. 339, Chicago, Illinois, Lodge No. 370, St. Paul, Minnesota, Lodge No. 1163, Chicago, Illinois, Lodge No. 1296, Omaha, Nebraska, and Lodge No. 1337, Minneapolis, Minnesota effective October 1, 1968
    - Lodge No. 1018, Chicago Great Western Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1922-1959 (Box 138, Folder 33)
      March 22, 1922-October 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-1023. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1023, Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railway Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1968 (Box 138, Folder 34)
      December 11, 1929-August 29, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 68, Chicago, Illinois, Lodge 554, St. Louis, Missouri, Lodge 774, Chicago, Illinois, and Lodge 983, Chicago, Illinois effective August 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1025. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1025, Chicago Great Western Lodge, Fort Dodge, Iowa, 1941-1968 (Box 138, Folder 35)
      September 4, 1941-November 12, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 369, Boone, Iowa effective October 1, 1968 / Lodge No. 1025, Boone, Iowa / Lodge No. 1025, Des Moines, Iowa
  - Sub-Series 235-1026. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1026, Pioneer Northwest Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1927-1957 (Box 138, Folder 36)
      December 28, 1927-June 27, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-1029. Local Lodges